{
    "subject": "resource/Joyalukkas",
    "predicate": "property/products",
    "object": "Jewellery",
    "human_readable": "Joyalukkas produces Jewellery.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8826023936271667,
            "question": "What does Joyalukkas produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6684215068817139,
            "question": "Joyalukkas specializes in manufacturing what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6561042070388794,
            "question": "Is Joyalukkas known for making something specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6559368968009949,
            "question": "What kind of products are made by Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6446402668952942,
            "question": "Joyalukkas is associated with which industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6326619386672974,
            "question": "What type of items does the company Joyalukkas create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5740960836410522,
            "question": "What is the primary output of Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4761868119239807,
            "question": "What goods are associated with the brand Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4697391986846924,
            "question": "What do people commonly buy from Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3245546221733093,
            "question": "What is Joyalukkas' main business activity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joyalukkas produces Jewellery.",
            "html": "dbpedia_873_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do people commonly buy from Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_873_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What goods are associated with the brand Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_873_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary output of Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_873_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_873_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Joyalukkas is involved in the production and retail of various types of jewellery, including diamond, gold, silver, and gemstone-studded pieces. Therefore, the statement \"Joyalukkas produces Jewellery\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}